<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google on Luca Berton&#39;s Website, Blog and all the Cool Stuff. Web is my playground!</title>
    <link>https://mrevolution.eu/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google on Luca Berton&#39;s Website, Blog and all the Cool Stuff. Web is my playground!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mrevolution.eu/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Mobile Web Specialist Nanodegree</title>
      <link>https://mrevolution.eu/blog/mobile-web-specialist-nanodegree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrevolution.eu/blog/mobile-web-specialist-nanodegree/</guid>
      <description>I was selected for a full 6-month Mobile Web Specialist Nanodegree - Google Developer Scholarship EMEA program (1.000 seats) after 3 months of Google Developer Challenge (10.000 seats). Excited about this opportunity! Thank you Udacity &amp;amp; Google</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google WebFundamentals contributions</title>
      <link>https://mrevolution.eu/blog/google-webfundamentals-contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrevolution.eu/blog/google-webfundamentals-contributions/</guid>
      <description>In these few months I&amp;rsquo;ve been contributing to Google WebFundamentals project as contributor and Italian moderator and translator.
List of approved translations:
 Performance Misurazione performance con il modello RAIL Comprendere la bassa larghezza di banda e la latenza elevata Introduzione a HTTP/2 Il modello PRPL Priorizzare le risorse: fare in modo che il browser ti sia d&amp;rsquo;aiuto Performance di rendering Evita i layout grandi, complessi e schiaccianti Utilizza proprietà del componente di composizione e gestisci il conteggio dei livelli Ridurre i rimbalzi dei gestori di input Semplifica la complessità di Paint e riduci le Aree di Paint Riduci l&amp;rsquo;ambito e la complessità dei calcoli di stile Ottimizza l&amp;rsquo;esecuzione di JavaScript Riproduzione veloce con il precaricamento dei video Coursi Udacity  List of approved proofreading:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Academy for Ads achievements</title>
      <link>https://mrevolution.eu/blog/google-academy-for-ads-achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrevolution.eu/blog/google-academy-for-ads-achievements/</guid>
      <description>Achievements earned in Google Academy for Ads:
 Google Web Designer Basics certificate (passed on 9th October 2017) DoubleClick Dynamic Creative Basics certificate (passed on 6th November 2017)  I&amp;rsquo;m on the Rich Media Gallery Certified Users list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes contributions</title>
      <link>https://mrevolution.eu/blog/kubernetes-contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 11:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrevolution.eu/blog/kubernetes-contributions/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been started my contribution to Kubernetes project (Production-Grade Container Orchestration).
My Italian translation is part of the release 1.8 (details on pull request).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>